gamehag.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy policy | Gamehag

Privacy Policy

### § 1 Object and principles of the Privacy Policy

  1. This Privacy Policy sets out the principles of processing and protection of personal information pertaining to Users of the www.gamehag.com Portal. It constitutes an integral part of the Terms and Conditions of the www.gamehag.com website. 

  2. The www.gamehag.com website respects Users’ right to privacy and makes every effort to ensure the most comprehensive protection of the personal information entrusted to it.

  3. The Administrator of the personal information provided by Users is Gaming Sp. z o.o., ul. Romana Abrahama 18, 61-615 Poznań, NIP [VAT reg. No.]: 7831749141, REGON [statistical ID No.]: 365698526, entered in the Register of Entrepreneurs kept by the District Court for Poznań - Nowe Miasto and Wilda in Poznań, 8th Commercial Division of the National Court Register under number KRS 0000643377.

  4. The Administrator shall protect the personal information against unauthorised access, loss, alteration, damage or destruction and shall process the information entrusted thereto in conformity with the legal regulations in force, and in particular in conformity with the requirements of the Personal Information Protection Act of 29 August 1997.

### § 2 Type and purpose of processed personal information

  1. Personal information is processed on the basis of a consent granted by the User upon registration with the Portal.

  2. Personal information referred to in § 2.1 above includes particulars enabling identification of the User and determining his identity, i.e.:   
– first name and surname,   
– age,   
– address of residence,   
– e-mail address,   
– mobile phone number.

  3. Personal information provided by the Portal User shall be processed exclusively for the purpose of using the Portal.

  4. The User shall have the right of access, monitoring and verification of the processed information pertaining thereto and the right to obtain information on the purpose, scope and method of processing of the data contained in the files, the right to demand supplementing, updating and correcting such data, temporary or permanent suspension of processing thereof, removal of data, as well as to demand that the data no longer be processed pursuant to Article 32 clause 1 item 7 of the Personal Information Protection Act and to file a protest pursuant to Article 32 clause 1 item 8 of the Personal Information Protection Act.

  5. The User hereby warrants and represents that all personal information provided thereby in the course of registration or while using the Portal is true and complete. Providing true and complete personal information is a prerequisite for the uninterrupted and correct use of the Portal.

### § 3 Account cancellation

  1. The User may at any time cancel his account with the Website.

  2. Cancellation of the User’s account results in the removal of any and all information and data pertaining to the User. The Portal Administrator, however, reserves the right to store the User’s information and to refuse to remove it to the extent and for a period which is legally permitted, this in order to settle any obligations that have arisen between the User and the Portal and in order to clarify the circumstances of an unauthorised use of the Portal, i.e. its use in breach of the Terms and Conditions and/or legal provisions in force.

### § 4 Cookies

Use of cookies 
  1. Cookies are small text files downloaded onto the User’s device while using the website, used to identify the User or to store the history of activities undertaken thereby.

  2. Cookies are used to adjust and optimise the contents of the Website to the Users’ preferences, to produce statistics of website usage, to personalise marketing content and to ensure Website security.

  3. The User may disagree with the use of cookies on his device, among others by changing browser settings. Refusal to agree to the use of cookies may, however, result in incorrect functioning of the Website or its incomplete display.

### § 5 Final provisions

  1. Users may send any questions and objections to this Privacy Policy to the following e-mail address: contact@gamehag.com

  2. This Privacy Policy may be amended. The Administrator shall notify Users thereof upon a seven days’ notice by publishing it on the Portal.
